{
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "a story\n\n---> two ___",
      "answer": "stories",
      "explain": "\n\n- story -> stories\nRemember: Nouns ending in - y preceded by a consonant -> changing - y to - ies.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a pen\n\n---> ten ___",
      "answer": "pens",
      "explain": "\n\n- pen -> pens",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a sportsman \n\n---> two ___ ",
      "answer": "sportsmen",
      "explain": "\n\n- sportsman -> sportsmen\n(irregular plural)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a portfolio\n\n---> seven ____",
      "answer": "portfolios",
      "explain": "\n\n- portfolio -> portfolios\nMost nouns ending in o preceded by a vowel -> +s.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a pencil\n\n---> ten ___",
      "answer": "pencils",
      "explain": "\n\n- pencil -> pencils",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a hat\n\n---> five ___",
      "answer": "hats",
      "explain": "\n\n- hat -> hats",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a monkey \n\n---> two ___ ",
      "answer": "monkeys",
      "explain": "\n\n- monkey -> monkeys\nRemember: Nouns ending in y preceded by a vowel -> + s.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a folio\n\n---> three ___",
      "answer": "folios",
      "explain": "\n\n- folio -> folios\nMost nouns ending in o preceded by a vowel -> +s.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a moss\n\n---> two ___",
      "answer": "mosses",
      "explain": "\n\n- moss -> mosses\nRemember: Nouns ending in s, z, x, sh, and ch -> + es.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "a valley\n\n---> four ____",
      "answer": "valleys",
      "explain": "\n\n- valley -> valleys\nRemember: Nouns ending in y preceded by a vowel -> + s.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "4"
    }
  ]
}